[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "Who walks away with the gold guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "I don't care what makes you so curious (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "What's the significance of Pistorius getting bail at this stage, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "You know, I don't think it surprised the legal experts.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Pistorius"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Should we read anything into that or is that a consistent thing in South African law?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "It's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Is that the sense you're getting among South Africans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Africans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Do you have absolute confidence that Oscar is telling the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "No, like I said before, the onus is on Oscar.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "What is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "It's basically used to fight the means of fatigue and tiredness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "What can you tell me about Oscar and alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Look, that's the magistrate's decision and what the magistrate wants during this bail, after this bail application.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "He does drink alcohol then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I'm sure when he goes out and goes for dinner with his friends and family, we'll have an occasional drink, but he's not an alcoholic if that's what you're asking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Are you ready for the next stage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "We don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "What are your concerns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "I have to read the conditions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Would you say the reality is he would have alcohol just not to access?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Look, I mean, that's obviously something he would do in his private time or he's off time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Have you reached out to him or any of his family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Briefly, I spoke to his brother, I called, just to send my wishes and that my thoughts are with him and his family as they are going through a hard time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "And if you did, what did you make of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Piers, I didn't know him intimately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "Had Reeva given you any indication of any problems with Oscar at all in the whole time that you knew she was seeing him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "I tried to keep my discussions with Reeva on a business level.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "How big could she have become do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "She was on the brink of explosion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Why don't you believe him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Well, Piers, I think the magistrate raised substantial questions today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, your response to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Well, there are holes in his story and if the holes are validated by the empirical evidence, by the forensic evidence, he'll be convicted.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Without that, is it fair to convict him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Absolutely, because motive is not necessary to prove.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Alan, we left viewers in a cliffhanger there, you were accused of going backwards, backtracking, what was your response to Gloria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "EX", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "I don't even know how to go backwards.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Gloria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Why did he have to fire four shots?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "That's like apples and oranges.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Pistorius"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Why not just one shot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "RB", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "The four shots thing I find a bit of a misnomer in terms of an argument against Pistorius, if he genuinely thought it was an intruder who is about to attack him, or fear for his life, you look at the number of cases in America where there are states for stand your ground.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria"]}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Why didn't he see if his girlfriend was OK and help her to run out the door?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "What are you saying, Gloria, it's based on calm, rational thought.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Isn't the reality in the heat of the moment, nobody knows how someone is going to behave?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Is it a lot more volatile than we may imagine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "I don't think the public image is misleading.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Does he like them to the point of obsession, I mean, how would you describe his relationship with guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I think he was obsessed with his own safety and his own vulnerability.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Did you get the sense that occasionally he would drink a lot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "When I was with him, it was in the lead-up to the Olympics, to the London Olympics, and I think he had some wine around the house, but he very specifically told me he wasn't drinking at that time in those months, because he said I train so hard, alcohol has the impact of diminishing your training a little bit, and why should I give up anything, even for a glass of wine, because I am working so hard to be as fit as I can be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "And in terms of his behavior around women, did you see anything untoward in that regard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "What do you think of skewing it towards a more musical performance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "I hear the length is quite long.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Daniel Radcliffe"]}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Ben, the musical stuff is fine, but if you're skewing it to a younger demographic audience, is it sensible?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "They are balancing it with having the cast of \"The Avengers\" present, Daniel Radcliffe will be presenting, as well as there's a tribute to the 50th anniversary of James Bond.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "But do you see any surprises there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Another mention for Quvenzhane, the young girl?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "My favorite film of the year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Are we all agreed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Short answer, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steven Spielberg"]}, "docId": "130222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Where's your money, then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I can't bet against Steven Spielberg.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]